Annaliisa Tongpattanakul

Phone: 1(425)229-8763 | Email: annaliisa.s@outlook.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/annaliisa-tongpattanakul-83146486

Github: https://github.com/AnnaliisaS

Portfolio: https://annaliisas.github.io/responsive-portfolio/

Summary

IT student with a background in customer service, healthcare, and aviation. Enjoys a life-long passion for learning. Due to previous roles, have extensive experience with collaboration, problem solving and dedication to customer satisfaction.

Technical Skills

Languages: HTML 5, CSS 3, JavaScript, Java, Python Libraries/Frameworks: jQuery, Bootstrap, Foundation Applications/Other: Visual Studio Code, Node.js

Projects

Project1: https://github.com/AnnaliisaS/project1 | https://annaliisas.github.io/project1/

Project1 (aka BookHunter) is a web search application that returns books based on user's criteria with the option to disregard those that they have already read. Users can click links to find local libraries or bookstores that might stock the book, see similar results on Amazon, and save stories for future reference.

Core Responsibilities were repository management and Front-End design regarding page styling and structure.

Technologies used were HTML5, CSS3, Foundation, JavaScript, APIs: OpenLibrary and Google Maps, and Look logo maker.

Education

BAS in Information Technology: American Public University, Charles Town, WV (2016 - current) Pursuing a BAS with a concentration in Programming.

Full-Stack Web Development Program: University of Washington, Bellevue, WA. (11/2019 - 04/2020) Coding bootcamp focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.

AAS: Bellevue College, Bellevue, WA. (2012-2015). Graduated with High Distinction.

Nursing Assistant Certificate Program: Blossom Nursing Assistant Training School, Kent, WA

Professional Pilot Program: Classic Helicopter Corporation, Auburn, WA Hold Commercial Pilot License with Instrument rating in rotorcraft/helicopters.

Employment History

Substitute Bus Driver: Lake Washington School District, Redmond, WA. (2019) Learned how to conduct pre-trip and post-trip inspections, passenger management, how to operate hydraulic wheelchair lift and use of route maps. *Key Accomplishments:*

· Obtained a Class B CDL, with Passenger & School Bus endorsements, Air Brake restriction removed

Front Desk/Cashier: K1Speed, Bellevue, WA. (2018 – 2019)

Provided excellent customer service, helped customers with questions and/or concerns both in person and over the phone, accurately handled Point of Sale operations to ring up customers for purchases, coordinated and scheduled races precisely and efficiently, gave drivers safety briefings as necessary, and maintained the front desk area so it was clean, stocked, and organized at all times. *Key Accomplishments*:

• Helped management train new cashiers and Front Desk Supervisors as needed.

Tutor: Renton Technical College, Renton, WA. (2015 – 2015)

Provided tutoring services for students in the Surgical Technologist Program. Assessed students and provided guidance on study habits, as well as assisted them in their learning of material utilizing a variety of tools/methods tailored to their needs.

Surgical Services Patient/Family Ambassador: Overlake Medical Center, Bellevue, WA. (2013 – 2014) Volunteer role, spent 112 hours in the Perioperative Care Unit helping to transport patients, relay communications between patients and family in the waiting room, and performed light housekeeping duties.

Front Desk/Cashier: The Aviator's Store, Seattle, WA. (2007 – 2013)

Provided excellent customer service, conducted accurate cash handling, point of sale operations, answered multi-line telephones and received sales orders from business clients. *Key Accomplishments*:

• Trusted to ensure smooth business operations when the owner and manager were absent to attend trade-shows. Helped management train new cashiers as needed.